之前在急诊室
PREVIOUSLY ON E.R.:
干得漂亮。
THAT WAS A GREAT SAVE.
我其实是说做你的全职私人助理。
ACTUALLY, I MEANT BEING
YOUR FULL-TIME P.A.
太好了。我喜欢。
GREAT. I'D LOVE THAT.
这更多是走个形式。
THIS IS MORE OF A FORMALITY
THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
也许对你来说是，但你是我唯一的实习生。
MAYBE FOR YOU, BUT YOU'RE
THE ONLY INTERN I HAVE.
我佩服你的毅力。
I ADMIRE YOUR FORTITUDE.
我可受不了戴尔那种卑鄙小人的指使。
I COULDN'T HANDLE TAKING ORDERS
FROM A WEASEL LIKE DALE.
你的陈述达到了我们的所有预期。
YOUR PRESENTATION
WAS EVERYTHING WE EXPECTED.
这太荒谬了，露西。
THIS IS RIDICULOUS, LUCY.
所有人都觉得你可以。
EVERYONE THINKS YOU CAN.
我要去找卡特医生谈谈。
I'M GOING TO TALK
TO DR. CARTER.
我还没扎过静脉。我不知道怎么做。
I HAVEN'T STARTED AN I.V.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
我从来没有。
I NEVER HAVE.
如果你再骗我
IF YOU EVER
LIE TO ME AGAIN
你就可以找别的轮岗了。
YOU CAN LOOK
FOR ANOTHER ROTATION.
啊！抱歉。
AAH! SORRY.
她正在分娩。
SHE'S IN
ACTIVE LABOR.
羊水在救护车里破了。
WATER BROKE
IN THE RIG.
可能得直接接生了。
PROBABLY HAVE
TO PLAY CATCH.
杰瑞，你在后面偷吃晚饭吗？
JERRY, SCARFING A LITTLE
EARLY DINNER BACK THERE?
什么？
WHAT?
哦，不。好一个，春妮。
OH, NO. GOOD ONE, CHUNY.
（笑）
( chuckles )
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝。
BABY, BABY, BABY.
这是我们的准妈妈吗？
THIS OUR
MOTHER-TO-BE?
猜对了。她的名字叫可可。
GOOD GUESS.
FIRST NAME'S COCO.
没有姓，没有地址。
NO LAST NAME,
NO ADDRESS.
在人行横道上晕倒了。
COLLAPSED IN
A CROSSWALK.
走，别走，别说话。
WALK, DON'T WALK,
DON'T TALK.
她的生命体征稳定。
HER VITALS
ARE STABLE.
哦，我能感觉到头了。
OOH, I CAN FEEL THE HEAD.
开了一条线。我们往下面看了一眼
STARTED A LINE.
WE TOOK A PEEK
DOWN SOUTH
她还没临盆。
AND SHE'S NOT CROWNING.
给我加冕，我是女王，王子要来了。
CROWN ME, I'M THE QUEEN,
AND THE PRINCE IS COMING.
* 绕着山转... *
* COMING 'ROUND
THE MOUNTAIN... *
可可，你的预产期是什么时候？
WHEN'S YOUR DUE DATE, COCO?
我不喜欢约会。太甜了。哦！
I DON'T LIKE DATES.
TOO SWEET. OH!
大的。大痛苦。
BIG ONE.
BIG PAIN.
哦……哦。
OH... OH.
你以前接生过孩子吗？
HAVE YOU DELIVERED
A BABY BEFORE?
不接生。
NO DELIVERY.
我们去三号帘子区。
LET'S GO
TO CURTAIN AREA THREE.
B.O.A.工具包，胎儿监护仪。
B.O.A. KIT, FETAL MONITOR.
婴儿保温箱。拿出来！
BABY WARMER.
TAKE IT OUT!
嘿，杰瑞，帮我呼叫产科。
HEY, JERRY,
PAGE O.B. FOR ME.
没问题。伙计，鹰已降落。
YOU GOT IT.
DUDE, THE EAGLE HAS LANDED.
哦，莉迪亚，我想你没收到我的备忘录。
OH, LYDIA, I GUESS
YOU DIDN'T GET MY MEMO.
下午 这班不穿戏服。
THE P.M. SHIFT
IS NOT WEARING
COSTUMES THIS YEAR.
会吓到病人。
IT SCARES THE PATIENTS.
这些年来，人们对这双美腿说了不少话
A LOT OF THINGS HAVE BEEN SAID
OVER THE YEARS
但“吓人”绝不是其中之一。
ABOUT THIS SET OF GAMS,
BUT "SCARY" ISN'T ONE OF THEM.
嗯，你知道，那也不是很专业
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT ALSO
ISN'T VERY PROFESSIONAL
所以如果你不介意换一下……
SO IF YOU WOULDN'T
MIND CHANGING...
我实际上买了一些这些小南瓜灯别针
I ACTUALLY GOT SOME OF THESE
LITTLE JACK-O-LANTERN PINS
给那些想庆祝节日的人。
FOR THOSE WHO WANT
TO SIGNIFY THE HOLIDAY.
好玩。
FUN.
我很高兴我的无服装备忘录传达给了一些人。
I'M GLAD MY NO-COSTUME MEMO
MADE IT TO SOME PEOPLE.
这是我的服装。
THIS IS MY COSTUME.
我打扮成一个彻头彻尾的呆板的人。
I'M DRESSED
AS A TOTAL STIFF.
所以……我想我可以破例。
SO... I GUESS I CAN MAKE
AN EXCEPTION.
一名四岁儿童颈部有严重穿刺伤。
FOUR-YEAR-OLD CHILD WITH SEVERE
PUNCTURE WOUNDS TO THE NECK.
这孩子为什么不在抢救室？
WHY ISN'T THIS KID
IN THE TRAUMA ROOM?
你说过你想看儿科的所有孩子……
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO SEE
ALL THE CHILDREN IN PEDES...
我现在要一个插管托盘，好吗？
I WANT AN INTUBATION TRAY NOW,
ALL RIGHT?
我要你四单位的血。
AND I WANT FOUR UNITS
OF YOUR BLOOD.
（笑）
( laughs )
哦，拜托。这很好笑。
OH, COME ON.
THIS IS FUNNY.
我只是觉得不合适，就这样。
I JUST DIDN'T THINK IT WAS
APPROPRIATE, THAT'S ALL.
但在急诊室的每部电话上都涂满了手术润滑剂，这就可以吗？
BUT PUTTING SURGILUBE
ALL OVER EVERY PHONE
IN THE E.R., THAT'S OKAY?
但我不是整个急诊室的负责人。
BUT I WASN'T IN CHARGE
OF THE WHOLE E.R.
我是儿科急诊室的负责人。
I AM IN CHARGE
OF THE PEDES E.R.
好吧，这个玩笑是冲着你去的，道格，不是冲着儿科急诊室。
WELL, THE JOKE
WAS ON YOU, DOUG,
NOT ON THE PEDES E.R.
但这些天，这两者似乎是一回事。
BUT THAT SEEMS TO BE
ONE AND THE SAME THESE DAYS.
那是什么意思？
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
我今天早上收到的备忘录——
THE MEMO I GOT
IN MY BOX THIS MORNING--
我还以为是你的万圣节恶作剧呢。
I THOUGHT IT WAS
YOUR HALLOWEEN PRANK.
这有什么问题？什么？
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THIS? WHAT?
道格，“所有儿科病人
DOUG, "ALL PEDIATRIC PATIENTS
“出院前必须由罗斯医生检查。
"MUST BE SEEN BY DR. ROSS
PRIOR TO DISCHARGE.
罗斯医生将对所有儿科病人进行每日复查。”
DR. ROSS WILL CONDUCT
A DAILY REVIEW ON ALL
PEDIATRIC PATIENTS."
对。那有什么问题？
RIGHT. WHAT'S
WRONG WITH THAT?
意思是你要签凯瑞·韦弗的病历。
MEANS YOU HAVE TO SIGN OFF
ON KERRY WEAVER'S CHARTS.
是啊，还有马克。
YEAH, AND MARK.
是啊，所以你很高兴。
YEAH, SO
YOU'RE PSYCHED.
嗯，是时候改变了，就这样。
WELL, IT'S TIME FOR
A CHANGE, THAT'S ALL.
是啊，有点像我。
YEAH, KIND OF LIKE ME.
我今天早上醒来，我是一只特兰西瓦尼亚蝙蝠。
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING,
I WAS A TRANSYLVANIAN BAT.
好了，够了，好吗？
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH, OKAY?
祝你好运。
GOOD LUCK.
卡罗尔，你能进来一下吗？
CAROL, COULD YOU
COME IN HERE?
（女人呻吟）
( woman moaning )
怎么了？
WHAT'S UP?
可可声称怀孕九个月了。
COCO HERE CLAIMS TO BE
NINE MONTHS' PREGNANT.
试着听胎心音。
TRY FOR FETAL
HEART TONES.
我没找到。
I COULDN'T
FIND THEM.
找到它们。
别弄丢了。
DON'T LOSE THEM.
去……去失物招领处找找。
LOOK IN THE...
LOOK IN THE LOST AND FOUND.
去……
LOOK IN THE...
子宫颈未扩张。
CERVIX ISN'T DILATED.
无附件肿块。
NO ADNEXAL MASSES.
她看起来确实怀孕了。
SHE SURE LOOKS PREGNANT.
我要生孩子了。
I'M HAVING A BABY.
我能
ALL I CAN
APPRECIATE
判断的
IS A NORMAL UTERUS
AND ABOUT TWO LITERS OF URINE
是一个正常的子宫和膀胱里大约两升尿液。
IN HER BLADDER.
可可，我们要给你
COCO, WE'RE GOING
TO GIVE YOU
一个便盆。
A BEDPAN.
你能放松一下，自己排尿吗？
CAN YOU TRY AND RELAX
AND RELIEVE YOURSELF?
浅呼吸。
SHALLOW BREATH.
自然的方式。
NATURE'S WAY.
要我去拿导尿管吗？
WANT ME TO
GET A FOLEY?
是的。还要一份尿液毒理学筛查。
YEAH. AND A URINE
TOX SCREEN.
顺便叫精神科。
CALL PSYCH WHILE
YOU'RE AT IT.
我真不敢相信你要穿那件衣服一整天。
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE GOING
TO WEAR THAT ALL DAY.
是有点痒，但这是我来美国过的第一个万圣节。
IT HAS GOTTEN ITCHY,
BUT IT'S MY FIRST
HALLOWEEN IN THE STATES.
你什么意思？你去年就在这里了。
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU WERE HERE LAST YEAR.
是啊，但我整晚都被困在手术室
YEAH, BUT I WAS STUCK
IN THE O.R. ALL NIGHT
所以没有万圣节讨糖，没有咬苹果，没有坐干草车……
SO NO TRICK-OR-TREATING,
APPLE BOBBING, HAYRIDES...
干草车？
HAYRIDES?
是啊，你们不是这样庆祝万圣节的吗——
YEAH, ISN'T THAT HOW YOU
CELEBRATE HALLOWEEN--
坐在装满干草的车里
RIDING IN A CART
FULL OF HAY
和你的甜心在星空下？
WITH YOUR SWEETIE
UNDER THE STARS?
伊丽莎白，芝加哥没有干草车。
ELIZABETH, THERE ARE
NO HAY CARTS IN CHICAGO.
你懂我的意思。
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
万圣节的重点是庆祝夜晚。
IT'S ALL ABOUT
CELEBRATING
THE NIGHT.
庆祝什么，嗯？
CELEBRATING WHAT, HUH?
孩子们把牙齿蛀掉，胃不舒服
KIDS ROTTING THEIR TEETH OUT,
GETTING SICK TO THEIR STOMACH
人们穿着这些愚蠢的……
PEOPLE WEARING
THESE STUPID...
我讨厌服装，你知道吗？
I HAVE A THING
AGAINST COSTUMES, YOU KNOW?
你肯定想过要成为某个人。
THERE MUST'VE BEEN SOMEONE
YOU WANTED TO BE.
我是医生。那就是我想成为的人。
I'M A DOCTOR.
THAT'S WHO I WANTED TO BE.
是的，但是作为孩子。
YES, BUT AS A CHILD.
你肯定想成为宇航员或足球运动员。
YOU MUST'VE WANTED TO BE
A SPACEMAN OR A FOOTBALLER.
没有。
NOPE.
你真是非凡，彼得。
YOU REALLY ARE
EXTRAORDINARY, PETER.
穿闪亮盔甲的骑士怎么样？
HOW ABOUT A KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOR?
不。牛仔。
NO.
A COWBOY.
不。听着，如果你想庆祝
NO. LISTEN, IF YOU
WANT TO CELEBRATE
我们为什么不去登普西家？
WHY DON'T WE GO
TO DEMPSEY'S?
他们有很棒的食物，还有，那是什么？
THEY GOT GREAT FOOD
AND, UH, WHAT IS THAT?
摇摆舞。
SWING DANCING.
伊丽莎白，你在这儿。
ELIZABETH,
THERE YOU ARE.
我的乙状结肠扭转已经标红送手术室了。
MY SIGMOID VOLVULUS
IS RED-LINED TO THE O.R.
而且术前化验单不在病历上。
AND THE PRE-OP LABS
AREN'T ON THE CHART.
我刚查了电脑。
I JUST CHECKED
THE COMPUTER.
除了电解质，所有结果都回来了。
EVERYTHING'S BACK
EXCEPT THE ELECTROLYTES.
光查电脑还不够。
CHECKING THE COMPUTER
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
我刚打电话给化验室，样本溶血了。
I JUST CALLED THE LAB AND
THE SPECIMEN WAS HEMOLYZED.
我打电话给采血科。
I'LL CALL PHLEBOTOMY.
太慢了。
TAKES TOO LONG.
我要你自己重新抽血
I WANT YOU TO
REDRAW YOURSELF
然后亲手送到化验室。
AND HAND-CARRY
IT TO THE LAB.
是，先生。
YES, SIR.
打扰一下。
EXCUSE ME.
请稍等。
JUST A MINUTE.
嗯？
YEAH?
我找格林医生。
I'M LOOKING
FOR DR. GREENE.
哦，该死！
OH, DAMN!
我需要保存那个。
I NEEDED
TO SAVE THAT.
那格林医生在哪里能找到？
SO I CAN FIND
DR. GREENE WHERE?
是啊，你得在椅子上等。
YEAH, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO WAIT IN CHAIRS.
好的。
OKEYDOKE.
杰瑞，系统工程师看过了吗？
JERRY, HAS THE SYSTEMS GUY
TAKEN A LOOK AT THIS YET?
他看了，但没碰。
HE LOOKED,
BUT HE DIDN'T TOUCH.
工作单没有会签。
THE WORK ORDER WASN'T CO-SIGNED.
莉莉，你拿的是什么？
LILY, WHAT DO
YOU GOT THERE?
这东西就放在救护车停放区。
THIS WAS JUST SITTING
OUT IN THE AMBULANCE BAY.
看，这个包里还有各种各样的东西。
LOOK, THERE'S ALL KINDS OF STUFF
IN THIS BAG, TOO.
纱布，皮肤缝合条，静脉输液管。
FOUR BY FOURS, STERI-STRIPS,
I.V. TUBING.
是啊，你知道吗？
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
我来处理这个。
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
真的吗？你确定？
REALLY? YOU SURE?
是的。没问题。
YEAH. NO WORRIES.
谢谢。当然。
THANKS.
SURE.
嘿，杰瑞。
HEY, JERRY.
嗨。
HI.
所以你不能推掉吗？
SO YOU CAN'T BLOW IT OFF?
哦，别误会我。
OH, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
我很想参加你的聚会
I WOULD LOVE
TO ATTEND YOUR SHINDIG
但这是工会派对。
BUT THIS IS
A TEAMSTER PARTY.
啊，你的眼睛闪耀着残疾政策的光芒。
AH, YOUR EYES ARE AGLOW WITH
THE FIRE OF DISABILITY POLICIES.
嗯，很少有保险承保人
WELL, IT'S RARE
THAT A POLICY UNDERWRITER
有机会在一个房间里
HAS AN OPPORTUNITY
AT A WHOLE ROOM
坐满喝醉的体力劳动者。
FULL OF DRUNKEN
MANUAL LABORERS.
听起来比做宿舍派对的监督员好。
SOUNDS BETTER
THAN CHAPERONING
A DORM PARTY.
所有人都知道烂派对最好的部分就是偷偷溜走
EVERYBODY KNOWS THE BEST PART
OF A BAD PARTY IS SNEAKING OUT
最好不要一个人。
PREFERABLY NOT ALONE.
所以我可能稍后会见到你。
SO I MIGHT
SEE YOU LATER.
或者我补偿你。
OR I'LL MAKE
IT UP TO YOU.
卡特医生，你好。
DR. CARTER, HI.
嗯，我拿到了肘部X光片……
UM, I GOT THE ELBOW FILMS
BACK ON...
露西，你能给我们点时间吗？
LUCY, CAN YOU GIVE
US A SECOND, PLEASE?
好的。
SURE.
什么？你说什么？
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
我拿到了卡汉先生肘部的X光片
I GOT THE ELBOW FILMS BACK
ON MR. CAHAN
和他的尼科洛拉的血常规和生化检查。
AND THE C.B.C. AND CHEM PANEL
ON HIS NICOLORA.
谢谢。看起来不错。
THANKS. LOOKS GOOD.
是啊，我吃饭的时候还在想你
YEAH, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT YOU AT DINNER
然后我发现我把这东西落在车里了。
AND I REALIZED
THAT I LEFT THIS IN MY CAR.
那是给派对用的吗？
IS THAT FOR THE PARTY?
不。我觉得你应该开始练习扎静脉了。
NO. I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD
START PRACTICING YOUR I.V.s.
我一直在练习。
I HAVE BEEN PRACTICING.
那这对你来说应该是小菜一碟了。
THEN THIS SHOULD
BE OLD HAT FOR YOU.
卡特医生，好。嘿……
DR. CARTER, GOOD.
HEY...
那些东西很重。
THOSE SUCKERS ARE HEAVY.
这些是什么？
WHAT ARE THESE?
明天的科室会议：
TOMORROW'S DEPARTMENTAL
CONFERENCE:
“老年人急性腹痛”。
"THE ACUTE ABDOMEN
IN THE ELDERLY."
我找出了你几个月前的一个缺血性肠道病例。
I PULLED AN ISCHEMIC BOWEL
YOU HAD A FEW MONTHS AGO.
我希望你能做报告。
I WAS HOPING
THAT YOU COULD PRESENT.
我从来没做过。
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
嗯，这是很好的经验
WELL, IT'S
GREAT EXPERIENCE
如果你认真想成为住院总医师。
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT BECOMING CHIEF RESIDENT.
哦，我很认真。
OH, I'M SERIOUS.
好的。我期待你的报告。
OKAY. I LOOK FORWARD
TO YOUR PRESENTATION.
住院总医师。很酷。
CHIEF RESIDENT.
PRETTY COOL.
是啊，很酷。
YEAH, PRETTY COOL.
进来了。
INCOMING.
我来。
I GOT IT.
我们有什么？乔·查塔洛夫斯基，40岁。
WHAT DO WE GOT?
JOE CHATTAROWSKI, 40.
在幸运酒铺前喝了一夸脱伏特加。
WAS DRINKING A QUART OF VODKA
IN FRONT OF LUCKY LIQUOR.
醉得走不动了，就打了911。
CALLED 911 WHEN HE WAS
TOO DRUNK TO WALK.
我需要帮助，医生。检查二。
I NEED HELP, DOC.
EXAM TWO.
你每天都喝酒吗，查塔洛夫斯基先生？
DO YOU DRINK EVERY DAY,
MR. CHATTAROWSKI?
是啊。但我想戒。
YEAH. BUT I WANT TO QUIT.
你是认真的吗？
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
我是认真的。
I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
你不是只是想
YOU'RE NOT
JUST LOOKING
找个地方睡觉吗？
FOR A PLACE TO
SLEEP IT OFF?
以我母亲的名义。
ON MY MOTHER'S EYES.
请问能帮我办理戒毒入院吗？
CAN YOU ADMIT ME
FOR DETOX, PLEASE?
卡特医生？
DR. CARTER?
我想奈特小姐可以帮你。
I THINK MISS KNIGHT
CAN HELP YOU WITH THAT.
看看能不能给他找个戒毒床位。
SEE IF YOU CAN FIND HIM
A DETOX BED.
然后你就可以在那只教学手臂上练习了。
THEN YOU CAN PRACTICE
ON THAT TEACHING ARM.
好的，我们把他转过去。
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S TRANSFER HIM.
准备好了吗？一，二，三。
READY? ONE, TWO, THREE.
日均病人数是150人。
AVERAGE DAILY
CENSUS IS 150.
贝尔维尤医院每天看275人。
WE SEE 275 A DAY
AT BELLEVUE.
令人印象深刻。
IMPRESSIVE.
我们是世界上第二大急诊科。
WE'RE THE SECOND-LARGEST
EMERGENCY DEPARTMENT
IN THE WORLD.
我带你去创伤室。
I'LL SHOW YOU
THE TRAUMA ROOMS.
嘘，嘿，杰瑞。
PSST, HEY, JERRY.
嗯。那个人是谁？
HMM.
WHO'S THAT?
和格林医生在一起的？是啊。
WITH DR. GREENE?
YEAH.
那是来自纽约的利特瓦克医生。
THAT IS DR. LITVAK
FROM NEW YORK.
丹·利特瓦克？
DAN LITVAK?
是的。
YEAH. I THINK HE'S HERE
INTERVIEWING TO BE E.R. CHIEF.
我想他来这里面试急诊科主任。
OH, MY GOD.
哦，我的天。
DAN LITVAK-- HE'S NATIONAL CHAIR
OF THE ACEP PANEL
丹·利特瓦克——他是ACEP实践指南小组的全国主席。
FOR PRACTICE GUIDELINES.
上个月《年鉴》的头版文章。
LEAD ARTICLE
IN LAST MONTH'S ANNALS.
嗯，那很好，对吧？
WELL, THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
嘿，哥们。我是罗斯医生。你叫什么名字？
HEY, BUDDY. I'M DR. ROSS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
贾里德。
JARED.
穿上万圣节妆后立即出现瘙痒性皮疹。
PRURITIC RASH RIGHT AFTER
PUTTING ON HIS HALLOWEEN MAKEUP.
他身上长满了荨麻疹。
HE'S COVERED
WITH HIVES.
我们来看看他。
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT HIM.
他以前有过荨麻疹吗？
HAS HE HAD
HIVES BEFORE?
没有。
NO.
好的。
ALL RIGHT.
你嘴里有肿胀吗？
ANY SWELLING
IN YOUR MOUTH?
你呼吸困难吗？
ARE YOU HAVING
TROUBLE BREATHING?
我的舌头感觉很大。好的。
MY TONGUE FEELS BIG.
OKAY.
血压90/60，脉搏72。
B.P.'s 90/60, PULSE 72.
好的，给他皮下注射0.2肾上腺素，静脉注射25苯海拉明。
OKAY, LET'S GIVE HIM .2
OF SUB Q EPI, BENADRYL 25 I.V.
他会好起来吗？
IS HE GOING TO BE OKAY?
他有严重的过敏反应。
HE HAS A BAD
ALLERGIC REACTION.
我们需要用静脉药物治疗他
WE NEED TO TREAT HIM
WITH I.V. MEDICATION
然后观察他几个小时。
AND JUST WATCH HIM
FOR A FEW HOURS.
我还能去要糖吗？
CAN I STILL GO
TRICK-OR-TREATING?
我想不能了，甜心
I DON'T THINK SO,
SWEETIE
但我们可以在这里给你找些
BUT WE CAN FIND YOU
SOME FUN STUFF
好玩的东西
TO DO AROUND HERE.
好玩的东西在这里很烂。
FUN STUFF AROUND HERE SUCKS.
你把我孩子怎么了？
WHAT DID YOU DO
WITH MY BABY?
你把……？
WHAT DID YOU...?
我的孩子呢？
WHERE'S MY BABY?
我应该问吗？
SHOULD I ASK?
到目前为止已经排出2200毫升。肚子平了。
2,200cc's OUT SO FAR.
BELLY'S FLAT.
哦，我失去了我的孩子。
OH, I LOST MY BABY.
氟哌啶醇，肌注五毫克。
HALDOL, FIVE
MILLIGRAMS I.M.
凯瑞：马克，我正在找你上个月
Kerry:
MARK, I'M LOOKING FOR
YOUR CHART REVIEWS
未按时出院的病历复查。
ON LAST MONTH'S
UNSCHEDULED RETURNS.
呃，是啊，我把它们放在你盒子里了。
UH, YEAH, I PUT THEM
IN YOUR BOX.
凯瑞，这是丹·利特瓦克医生。
KERRY, THIS IS
DR. DAN LITVAK.
这是凯瑞·韦弗医生，我们的临时主任。
THIS IS DR. KERRY WEAVER,
OUR INTERIM CHIEF.
很高兴见到你。
NICE TO MEET YOU.
利特瓦克医生，你来自哪里？
WHERE YOU FROM, DR. LITVAK?
纽约，贝尔维尤医院。
NEW YORK, BELLEVUE.
只是来取经吗？
JUST HERE TO
GET A FEW TIPS?
不。我刚进行了主任职位的第二次面试。
NO. I JUST HAD
MY SECOND INTERVIEW
FOR THE CHIEF POSITION.
格林医生很友善地带我参观。
DR. GREENE IS BEING KIND ENOUGH
TO SHOW ME AROUND.
第二次面试。
SECOND INTERVIEW.
是啊，他们想，呃……和利特瓦克医生
YEAH, THEY WANTED TO, UH...
MEET WITH DR. LITVAK
再见一面在今晚的投票前。
ONE MORE TIME
BEFORE TONIGHT'S VOTE.
是啊，我以为投票要到下周三。
YEAH, I THOUGHT THE VOTE
WASN'T UNTIL NEXT WEDNESDAY.
我今晚要搭飞机去百慕大参加会议。
I HAVE TO HOP A PLANE
TO A CONFERENCE
IN BERMUDA TONIGHT.
他们觉得如果我能提前知道结果
THEY THOUGHT IT WOULD BE BEST
会最好。
IF I COULD KNOW
BEFOREHAND.
嗯，那太棒了。
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
越早越好，是吧？
THE SOONER
THE BETTER, HUH?
我想我还是去查一下我的邮箱吧。
I GUESS I'LL JUST
CHECK MY MAILBOX.
那就是竞争，是吧？
THAT'S THE COMPETITION, HUH?
你找到戒毒床位了吗？
DID YOU HAVE ANY LUCK
WITH THAT DETOX BED?
还没人给我回电话。
NO ONE CALLED ME BACK YET.
闪了一下……我进去了。
GOT A FLASH...
AND I AM IN.
是的，你进去了。
YES, YOU ARE.
我想我准备好真刀真枪干了。
I THINK I'M READY
FOR THE REAL THING NOW.
好吧，让我们看看。
WELL, LET'S FIND OUT.
我指导你处理查塔洛夫斯基先生的病例。
I'LL TALK YOU THROUGH
MR. CHATTAROWSKI.
好的。
OKAY.
确保我们不要重蹈上次静脉注射的覆辙。
MAKE SURE WE DON'T REPEAT
OUR LAST I.V. FIASCO.
那绝对不会再发生了。
THAT DEFINITELY
WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
不。那既是我的错，也是你的错。
NO. IT WAS MY FAULT
AS MUCH AS IT WAS YOURS.
哦，我可不这么认为。
OH, I WOULDN'T
EXACTLY SAY THAT.
嗯，我应该更密切地监督你。
WELL, I SHOULD'VE SUPERVISED YOU
A LITTLE BIT MORE CLOSELY.
决不应该让你走到那一步。
SHOULD NEVER HAVE LET YOU GET
TO THE PLACE THAT YOU DID.
从现在开始，我们一步一个脚印地来。
FROM NOW ON,
WE'LL JUST TAKE IT
从现在开始，我们一步一个脚印地来。
ONE STEP AT A TIME.
卡特，你的醉鬼跑了。
CARTER, YOUR DRUNK ELOPED.
查塔洛夫斯基？
CHATTAROWSKI?
那是说他走了吗？
DOES THAT MEAN
HE LEFT?
是的。
YEP.
还有人需要静脉注射吗？
DOES ANYONE ELSE
NEED AN I.V.?
我来。
I'VE GOT IT.
你想成为超级英雄——
YOU WANTED TO
BE A SUPERHERO--
紧身衣，披风……
TIGHTS, CAPE...
（笑）
( laughs )
是啊，错了。
YEAH, WRONG.
嗯，肯定有人，对吧？
WELL, THERE
WAS SOMEONE,
WASN'T THERE?
嘿，看谁来了。
HEY, LOOK
WHO'S HERE.
再见，小可爱。
BYE-BYE, CUTIE PIE.
嘿……
HEY...
嘿，小蜜蜂。
HEY, LITTLE BEE.
天啊，他长得真快。
GOSH, HE'S
GETTING
SO BIG.
他把我吃穷了。
HE'S EATING ME OUT
OF HOUSE AND HOME.
我没想到你会来。
I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU.
我们刚离开沃尔特和杰基家。
WE JUST LEFT WALT
AND JACKIE'S.
年度大派对？
THE ANNUAL BLOWOUT?
我告诉沃尔特
I TOLD WALT
他应该穿上他七十年代穿的
HE SHOULD PUT ON
ONE OF HIS SUPER
DUPER FLY OUTFITS
那些超级棒的衣服……
HE USED TO WEAR
IN THE '70s...
不，别鼓励他。
NAH, DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM.
那个兄弟仍然认为
THAT BROTHER STILL THINKS
涤纶会卷土重来。
POLYESTER'S GOING TO MAKE
A COMEBACK.
说到服装
SPEAKING
OF COSTUMES
你相机里还有胶卷吗？
DO YOU HAVE ANY FILM
LEFT IN THAT CAMERA?
是的。我们应该让他和爸爸一起拍。
YES. WE SHOULD HAVE HIM
WITH HIS DADDY.
绝对的。
ABSOLUTELY.
你愿意效劳吗？
WOULD YOU DO THE HONORS?
是啊，当然。
YEAH, SURE.
好的。
OKAY.
准备好了吗？
READY?
感觉好点了吗？
FEELING ANY BETTER?
我没事……我想。
I'M ALL RIGHT... I GUESS.
你给我……
WHAT DID YOU...?
你给我吃了什么？
WHAT DID YOU GIVE ME?
呃，氟哌啶醇……
UH, HALDOL...
让你平静下来。
TO CALM YOU DOWN.
我不能吃那个。
I CAN'T TAKE THAT.
对我的孩子不好。
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR MY BABY.
可可，你没有孩子。
COCO, YOU DON'T
HAVE A BABY.
但我会有的，真的。
BUT I WILL, REALLY.
我正处于孕早期。
I'M IN MY FIRST TRIMESTER.
可可……你没有怀孕。
COCO...
YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT.
你只是尿潴留。
YOU WERE JUST
RETAINING URINE.
卡罗尔……
CAROL...
你做过怀孕测试，是吗？
YOU DID DO A PREGNANCY TEST,
DIDN'T YOU?
开始希望我做过了。
STARTING TO WISH I HAD.
嗯，我……我是精神分裂症患者
UM, I'M-I'M SCHIZOPHRENIC
我一直在服用利培酮
AND I HAD BEEN TAKING
RESPIRADONE
但当我发现自己怀孕时
BUT WHEN I FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT
（声音颤抖）：我停药了，这样孩子才能好。
( voice breaking ):
I WENT OFF THE MEDICATION
SO THAT THE BABY WOULD BE OKAY.
氟哌啶醇对孩子有什么影响？
WHAT WILL THE HALDOL DO
TO THE BABY?
如果，事实上，你怀孕了
IF, IN FACT, YOU ARE PREGNANT
有肢体畸形的报告。
THERE ARE REPORTS
OF LIMB MALFORMATION.
哦，我的天啊。
OH, MY GOD.
我很抱歉，宝贝。
I'M SO SORRY, BABY.
好的。看起来心脏仍然是空的。
ALL RIGHT. LOOKS
LIKE THE HEART
IS STILL EMPTY.
再拿两单位。
LET'S GET TWO
MORE UNITS.
胸管涌血。超过两升了。
CHEST TUBE'S GUSHING.
IT'S OVER TWO LITERS.
可能是肺门损伤。好了，大家。
COULD BE A HILAR INJURY.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE.
准备好右侧开胸手术。快点。
LET'S SET UP FOR A RIGHT-SIDED
THORACOTOMY. LET'S MOVE.
十号刀片。我们做蛤壳式切口。
TEN BLADE.
WE'LL DO A CLAMSHELL.
马利克，给血库打电话。我们需要更多O型阴性血
MALIK, CALL
THE BLOOD BANK.
WE NEED MORE O-NEG
和血型特异性血，一旦准备好就送来。
AND TYPE SPECIFIC
WHEN IT'S READY.
好的。撑开器。彼得，切开胸骨。
OKAY. RIB SPREADER.
PETER, CUT ACROSS
THE STERNUM.
好的。我需要一把莱布什克刀。
ALL RIGHT. I NEED
A LEBSHKE KNIFE.
什么？
A WHAT?
一把莱布什克刀和一把槌子。快！
A LEBSHKE AND A MALLET.
LET'S MOVE!
韦弗：看。水槽旁的顶层抽屉。
Weaver:
LOOK. TOP DRAWER
BY THE SINK.
你真正需要的是一把胸骨锯。
WHAT YOU REALLY NEED
IS A STERNAL SAW.
胸骨锯是手术室的工具，不是急诊室的。
A STERNAL SAW IS A TOOL
FOR THE O.R., NOT THE E.R.
右胸充满了血。
THE RIGHT CHEST
IS FULL OF BLOOD.
血管钳。更多吸引。
VASCULAR CLAMP. MORE SUCTION.
本顿：找到源头了吗？
Benton:
LOCATE THE SOURCE?
啊哈。
AHH.
把你的手拿开，把你的手拿开。
MOVE YOUR HAND,
MOVE YOUR HAND.
心脏还是空的。
HEART'S
STILL EMPTY.
四单位血进去了。
FOUR UNITS IN.
他失血的速度比我们输血的速度快。
HE'S LOSING IT
FASTER THAN WE
CAN PUT IT IN.
该死！
DAMN!
血型特异性血来了。
TYPE SPECIFIC'S HERE.
挂两袋——快速输液器。
HANG TWO--
RAPID INFUSER.
我快到了。
I'M ALMOST THERE.
看起来是右心房。
LOOKS LIKE RIGHT ATRIUM.
O-聚乳酸现在。快点。
O-VICRYL NOW.
LET'S MOVE.
有更快的方法。
THERE WERE
FASTER WAYS TO DO THAT.
我怀孕了。
I AM PREGNANT.
测试证实了。
THE TEST CONFIRMED IT.
我们不知道氟哌啶醇是否影响了胎儿。
WE DON'T KNOW IF THE HALDOL
AFFECTED THE FETUS.
我们将通过超声监测怀孕情况。
WE'RE GOING TO MONITOR
THE PREGNANCY WITH ULTRASOUND.
也许我不应该生孩子。
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T
HAVE A BABY.
因为氟哌啶醇？
BECAUSE OF THE HALDOL?
我甚至没告诉我妈妈，你知道。
I DIDN'T EVEN TELL MY MOM,
YOU KNOW.
她那么骄傲
SHE WAS SO PROUD
我在中途之家。
THAT I WAS IN
THE HALFWAY HOUSE.
我以为会没事的。
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE OKAY.
我以为我可以停药，但是我……
I THOUGHT I COULD GO OFF
MY MEDS, BUT I...
不能，对吗？
CAN'T, CAN I?
你可能会有更多像这样的事件。
YOU'LL PROBABLY HAVE MORE
INCIDENTS LIKE THIS ONE.
我不该这样做。
I SHOULDN'T GO
THROUGH WITH THIS.
你在短时间内经历了太多。
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
IN A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME.
也许你应该等等。
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST WAIT.
我不该这样做。
I SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
（轻声）：我不该这样做。
( softly ):
I SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
我不该这样做。
I SHOULDN'T
DO THIS.
所以你觉得她会终止妊娠吗？
SO YOU THINK SHE'LL
TERMINATE HER PREGNANCY?
我就是这个印象。
THAT'S THE IMPRESSION I GOT.
对她和你来说可能都最好。
PROBABLY BE THE BEST
FOR HER AND FOR YOU.
是啊。让我摆脱困境。
YEAH. GETS ME
OFF THE HOOK.
你今晚想喝一杯吗？放松一下？
YOU WANT TO HAVE
A DRINK LATER?
DECOMPRESS?
我很想，但珍回来了
I WOULD,
BUT JEN'S BACK IN TOWN
我们得好好谈谈。
AND WE HAVE TO HAVE
ONE OF OUR TALKS.
哦。听起来今天不是你的日子，马克。
OH. SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
NOT YOUR DAY, MARK.
如果你想的话，你现在可以下班了，露西。
YOU CAN TAKE OFF NOW
IF YOU WANT, LUCY.
我们这里工作差不多了。
WE'RE PRETTY CAUGHT
UP AROUND HERE.
那儿科急诊室呢？
WHAT ABOUT
THE PEDES E.R.?
那里站满了人。
IT'S STANDING ROOM ONLY
IN THERE.
道格·罗斯状态很好，是吧？
DOUG ROSS IS IN
A GROOVE, HUH?
不。你可能会拖慢他。
NO. YOU'D PROBABLY
JUST SLOW HIM DOWN.
对。嗯，那给我更多时间
RIGHT. WELL, THAT
GIVES ME MORE TIME
为派对做准备。
TO GET READY FOR THE PARTY.
对不起。我不是想惹你……
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO UPSET THE...
这个家伙就在幸运酒铺前面，
FOUND THIS GUY
RIGHT BACK CHILLIN'
拿着一瓶夜火车酒，舒服地待着。
WITH A BOTTLE
OF NIGHT TRAIN IN
FRONT OF LUCKY'S.
你们的检查室需要一个旋转门。
YOU ALL NEED A
REVOLVING DOOR ON
YOUR EXAM ROOMS.
哦，哦，哦。好久不见，查塔洛夫斯基先生。
WELL, WELL, WELL. LONG TIME
NO SEE, MR. CHATTAROWSKI.
所以，你认识这家伙？
SO, YOU KNOW THIS GUY?
是啊。他早些时候来过。
YEAH. HAD HIM
IN EARLIER.
他进来是为了戒毒
HE CAME IN
LOOKING TO
BE DETOXED
然后我们在血检完成之前他就跑了。
AND THEN ELOPED
BEFORE WE COULD GET
THE BLOOD WORK DONE.
嗯，下次我就直接报警了。
WELL, NEXT TIME,
I'M JUST CALLING THE COPS.
我们来接他，好吗？反正你下班了。
WE CAN TAKE HIM
FROM HERE, OKAY?
YOU'RE OFF, ANYWAY.
谢谢。
THANKS.
二号帘区。
CURTAIN AREA TWO.
查塔洛夫斯基先生，我是格林医生。
MR. CHATTAROWSKI,
I'M DR. GREENE.
这是哈撒韦护士。
THIS IS NURSE HATHAWAY.
我们欢迎你回来。
WE'D LIKE TO
WELCOME YOU BACK.
我知道我搞砸了，医生。
I KNOW I SCREWED UP, DOC.
我天生就是个搞砸的人。
I'M A SCREWUP BY NATURE.
我想重新开始。
I WANT TO MAKE
A CLEAN START.
我真的想。
I REALLY DO.
查塔洛夫斯基先生，你不会有一个新的开始
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO MAKE A CLEAN START,
MR. CHATTAROWSKI
手里还拿着一瓶酒。
WITH A BOTTLE OF
BOOZE IN YOUR HAND.
那是我的最后一杯。
THAT WAS MY LAST DRINK.
我不会再毒害自己了，
I'M NOT GOING
TO POISON MYSELF
我保证。
NO MORE,
I PROMISE.
除了充血，眼睛看起来还行。
OTHER THAN BLOODSHOT,
THE EYES LOOK OKAY.
向前倾。
LEAN FORWARD.
我要戒酒戒毒。
I'M GOING TO GET
CLEAN AND SOBER.
你得安静点，我才能听你的肺。
YOU GOT TO BE QUIET
SO I CAN HEAR YOUR LUNGS.
找到一份工作，一所房子，一个栅栏……
GET A JOB AND A HOUSE
AND A PICKET FENCE...
嘘，嘘，嘘！嘘，嘘。
SHH, SHH, SHH! SHH, SHH.
血压130，触诊。
B.P.'s 130 PALP.
查塔洛夫斯基先生
MR. CHATTAROWSKI
我试着给你找一个戒毒床位
I'M GOING TO TRY AND
GET YOU A DETOX BED
但你必须答应我你会留下来。
BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME
YOU'LL STAY.
我保证。
I PROMISE.
我真的会的。
I REALLY DO.
我要戒毒戒酒。
I'M GOING TO GET CLEAN
AND SOBER.
好的。如果你能移到这张床上。
OKAY. IF YOU COULD JUST
SCOOT OVER TO THIS BED.
你觉得他会留下吗？
YOU THINK
HE'LL STAY?
嗯，我对可可女士很悲观
WELL, I WAS A CYNIC
WITH MS. COCO
结果你也看到了
AND WE SAW HOW
THAT WORKED OUT
所以从因果报应上说，我必须相信这个人。
SO KARMICALLY, I HAVE
TO BELIEVE THIS GUY.
好的，卡尔玛医生，但如果你不介意的话
OKAY, DR. KARMA,
BUT IF YOU DON'T MIND
我要把他的衣服锁起来，
I'M GOING TO LOCK
UP HIS CLOTHES
SO IT MAKES IT
这样他这次就更难逃跑了。
A LITTLE HARDER FOR HIM
TO ESCAPE THIS TIME.
好主意。
GOOD IDEA.
（尖叫）
( screaming )
阿曼达，你必须为我保持不动。
AMANDA, YOU HAVE
TO STAY STILL FOR ME.
只会疼一秒钟。
IT WILL ONLY HURT
FOR A SECOND.
不，爸爸！
NO, DADDY!
她做完后我会给你一些贴纸。
I'LL GIVE YOU
SOME STICKERS
WHEN SHE'S DONE.
我不要贴纸，爸爸。
I DON'T WANT STICKERS, DADDY.
这真的有必要吗？
IS THIS REALLY NECESSARY?
不幸的是，是的。我们必须抽血
UNFORTUNATELY, IT IS.
WE HAVE TO TAKE BLOOD
做检查。
TO DO THE TEST.
爸爸，我想回家。
DADDY, I WANT
TO GO HOME.
这里一切都好吗？
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT IN HERE?
医生，我的小女儿怕针。
DOCTOR, MY LITTLE GIRL'S
AFRAID OF NEEDLES.
有没有办法不用这些就给她做检查？
IS THERE A WAY TO TEST HER
WITHOUT ALL THIS?
事实上，有。
AS A MATTER OF
FACT, THERE IS.
我们有什么？
WHAT DO WE GOT?
芭比·克利格曼，11岁，机动车事故。
BARBIE KLIGMAN,
11-YEAR-OLD M.V.A.
后座乘客系着腰带。
BACKSEAT PASSENGER
WITH A LAP BELT.
主诉腹痛。
COMPLAINS
OF ABDOMINAL PAIN.
血压105/70，脉搏95。
B.P. 105/70,
PULSE 95.
做血常规，生化20项
LET'S GET A C.B.C., CHEM 20
血型和保留，以及尿常规。
TYPE AND HOLD,
AND DIP A URINE.
芭比，你的脖子疼吗？
BARBIE, DOES
YOUR NECK HURT?
不，只有我的肚子。
NO, JUST MY STOMACH.
血氧饱和度98，室内空气。
PULSE OX IS 98
ON ROOM AIR.
胸部清晰。
CHEST IS CLEAR.
戴尔同意你在这里吗？
DALE OKAY WITH
YOU BEING HERE?
应该没问题。
SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
瞳孔五毫米
PUPILS ARE
FIVE MILLIMETERS
对光反应。
AND REACT TO LIGHT.
她会好起来吗？
IS SHE GOING
TO BE OKAY?
我们正在照顾她。
WE'RE TAKING CARE OF HER.
珍妮：很好的安全带挫伤。
Jeanie:
PRETTY GOOD
SEAT BELT CONTUSION.
是啊。
YEAH.
肠鸣音消失。
BOWEL SOUNDS
ARE ABSENT.
血红蛋白14.1。
HEMOGLOBIN'S 14.1.
好的。听着，这疼吗？
OKAY. LISTEN, DOES THIS HURT?
哎哟！
OW!
怎么回事？
WHAT'S GOING ON?
她有安全带瘀伤，这可能表明
SHE HAS A SEAT BELT BRUISE
WHICH CAN INDICATE
小肠损伤。
SMALL BOWEL INJURY.
我们将进行CT扫描。
WE'LL DO
A CAT SCAN.
即使是阴性
EVEN IF IT'S NEGATIVE
她可能需要探查性手术。
SHE MAY NEED
EXPLORATORY SURGERY.
哦，我的天啊。
OH, MY GOD.
听着，你会没事的，芭比。
LOOK, YOU'LL BE
OKAY, BARBIE.
爸爸妈妈会在这里陪你的，好吗？
MOMMY AND DADDY WILL
BE HERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
就这么简单吗？
THAT'S ALL IT TAKES?
是的。这台机器通过离子电渗疗法
YEAH. THE MACHINE
DELIVERS LIDOCAINE
将利多卡因输送到皮肤
TO THE SKIN
BY IONOPHORESIS
所以没有针。
SO NO NEEDLES.
嘿。
HEY.
韦弗医生，我们又见面了。
DR. WEAVER,
WE MEET AGAIN.
我以为你要赶飞机呢。
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
A PLANE TO CATCH.
航班延误了。我想待在这里
FLIGHT DELAYED. I FIGURE
HANGING OUT HERE
总比喝机场兑水鸡尾酒好。
BEATS WATERED-DOWN
AIRPORT COCKTAILS.
介意我旁观吗？
MIND IF I PLAY
FLY ON THE WALL?
这是罗斯医生的儿科诊室。
IT'S DR. ROSS'
PEDES ROOM.
当然。随便待。
SURE. HANG OUT.
好了，亲爱的。
HERE WE GO,
SWEETHEART.
阿曼达，你好吗？
HOW ARE YOU,
AMANDA?
好的。
OKAY.
你没事吧？
YOU'RE OKAY?
现在，这个敷垫会麻痹你的皮肤，好吗？
NOW, THIS PAD
PUTS YOUR SKIN TO
SLEEP, ALL RIGHT?
所以你什么也感觉不到。
SO YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO FEEL ANYTHING.
闭上眼睛，亲爱的。
CLOSE YOUR EYES,
SWEETHEART.
你感觉到什么了吗？
DO YOU FEEL ANYTHING?
没有。
NO.
好的。
OKAY.
韦弗：太神奇了。
Weaver:
IT'S AMAZING.
我们试过用药膏麻木，但需要一个小时。
WE TRIED NUMBING IT
WITH A CREAM BUT IT
TAKES AN HOUR.
这太棒了，道格。
THIS IS GREAT, DOUG.
真的。它叫什么来着？
IT REALLY IS.
WHAT'S IT CALLED AGAIN?
“麻木”。
"NUMBY."
我们在贝尔维尤医院做了三期临床试验。
WE DID THE PHASE THREE
CLINICAL TRIALS AT BELLEVUE.
我们已经用了一年多了。
WE'VE BEEN USING IT
FOR OVER A YEAR NOW.
（清嗓子）
( clears throat )
嘿，卡特医生。
HEY, DR. CARTER.
不错的服装。
NICE COSTUME.
我感觉有点逊。
I FEEL KIND OF LAME.
没人穿衣服。
NOBODY ELSE DRESSED UP.
嗯，还早呢。人们可能还会来。
WELL, IT'S EARLY YET.
PEOPLE MAY STILL SHOW.
传单上说8点。
THE FLYER SAID 8:00.
你得记住这些是医学生。
YOU GOT TO REMEMBER
THESE ARE MED STUDENTS.
他们很忙。
THEY'RE BUSY.
你要来点潘趣酒吗？
DO YOU WANT
SOME PUNCH?
呃，稍后。
UH, LATER.
我得去图书馆找文章
I GOT TO GO PULL ARTICLES
AT THE LIBRARY
为了明天的会议
FOR THIS CONFERENCE TOMORROW
也就是说，如果你觉得这个派对能自己管理的话。
THAT IS, IF YOU THINK THIS
PARTY CAN CHAPERONE ITSELF.
我来照看。
I'LL LOOK AFTER THINGS.
是啊。你为什么不那样做呢？
YEAH. WHY DON'T YOU
DO THAT?
这女孩几岁了？
HOW OLD IS THIS GIRL?
本顿：十一岁。
Benton:
ELEVEN.
她脸上涂的闪粉是怎么回事？
WHAT'S WITH THE GLITTER
ON HER FACE?
她应该是个公主。
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE A PRINCESS.
戴尔，把它夹住。
DALE, GET A CLAMP ON THAT.
巴布科克钳，请。
BABCOCK, PLEASE.
好的。十二指肠周围有点出血。
OKAY. THERE'S A
LITTLE BLEEDING
AROUND THE DUODENUM.
我们进行科彻尔化并探查腹膜后。
LET'S KOCHERIZE AND EXPLORE
THE RETROPERITONEUM.
电刀。
BOVIE.
你万圣节有什么计划？
WHAT DO YOU HAVE PLANNED
FOR HALLOWEEN?
没什么特别的。
NOTHING SPECIAL.
我知道22号公路上有一家汽车旅馆；丛林主题房间。
I KNOW A MOTEL ON ROUTE 22;
JUNGLE THEME ROOMS.
梅茨剪刀。
METZ.
14号房间。垂下来的藤蔓——你是泰山，她是简
ROOM 14. HANGING VINES--
YOU TARZAN, SHE JANE
你懂我的意思吗？
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
不。我想我们还是留在城里吧。
NO. I THINK
WE'LL JUST STAY IN TOWN.
好的。胰腺看起来不错。
ALL RIGHT. THE
PANCREAS LOOKS GOOD.
这里没有肾损伤。
NO RENAL
INJURIES HERE.
等等。有一个肾下肿块。
HOLD ON. THERE'S
AN INFRARENAL MASS.
腰部淋巴结？
LUMBAR NODE?
不。感觉不对劲。
NO. IT DOESN'T
FEEL RIGHT.
它……它太橡皮了。
IT'S... IT'S TOO RUBBERY.
这边也有一个。
THERE'S ONE ON
THIS SIDE, TOO.
可能是淋巴瘤。
COULD BE LYMPHOMA.
我们送去做活检。
LET'S SEND FOR A BIOPSY.
15号。
NUMBER 15.
伊丽莎白，病房里一切都好吗？
EVERYTHING OKAY ON THE WARDS,
ELIZABETH?
是的。您需要我刷手进来吗？
YES. WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO SCRUB IN?
是的。我们需要你的帮助。
YEAH. WE COULD
USE YOUR HELP.
太棒了。
WONDERFUL.
我们刚刚给芭比做了
WE JUST BIOPSIED
AN ABNORMAL
一个异常淋巴结活检。
LYMPH NODE
ON BARBIE HERE.
你为什么不把这个样本送到病理科
WHY DON'T YOU RUN
THIS SPECIMEN DOWN TO PATHOLOGY
然后等着冰冻切片结果。
AND WAIT
ON THE FROZEN SECTION RESULTS.
我们的病人堆积如山。
OUR PATIENTS ARE STACKED
TO THE RAFTERS.
我们正在处理。
WE'RE GETTING TO THEM.
你需要让主急诊室处理溢出的病人。
YOU NEED TO LET THE MAIN E.R.
HANDLE THE OVERFLOW.
我必须看这些孩子。你看到了凯瑞发生的事情。
I HAVE TO SEE THESE
KIDS. YOU SAW WHAT
HAPPENED WITH KERRY.
今晚很忙，道格。
IT'S A BUSY
NIGHT, DOUG.
一个医生不能独自看所有病人。
ONE DOCTOR CAN'T SEE
THEM ALL BY HIMSELF.
（呼气）：好吧，好吧。
( exhaling ):
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
把溢出的病人送去主急诊室，但把孩子们的病历给我。
SEND THE OVERFLOW
TO THE MAIN E.R., BUT
SEND ME THE KIDS' CHARTS.
当然。
OF COURSE.
最严重的那些，送给我。
AND THE SICKEST ONES,
SEND THEM TO ME.
我不会有别的办法。
I WOULDN'T DO IT
ANY OTHER WAY.
你为什么这么早回来？
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK
SO EARLY?
我和艾瑞尔厌倦了要糖
ME AND ARIEL, WE WERE
SICK OF TRICK-OR-TREATING
而且妈妈要迟到了。
AND MOM'S RUNNING LATE.
你在看什么？
WHAT ARE YOU
WATCHING?
家庭三角恋。
FAMILY LOVE TRIANGLES.
教育电视，是吧？
EDUCATIONAL TV, HUH?
是啊。妈妈说
YEAH. MOM SAYS
当我们搬到圣路易斯
THAT WHEN WE MOVE
TO ST. LOUIS
她每天只让我看
SHE'S ONLY GOING
TO LET ME WATCH
一小时电视。
AN HOUR OF
TELEVISION A DAY.
当你搬到圣路易斯的时候？
WHEN YOU MOVE
TO ST. LOUIS?
你不知道？
YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
我想这就是为什么
I THINK THAT'S WHY
妈妈想见你。
MOM WANTED TO SEE YOU.
所以这事就这么定了？
SO IT'S A DONE DEAL THEN?
我的房间会大一倍
MY ROOM'S GOING TO BE
TWICE AS BIG
街对面有个公园可以遛狗。
AND THERE'S A PARK ACROSS
THE STREET FOR THE DOGS.
听起来不错。
IT SOUNDS NICE.
那里真的很漂亮。
IT'S REALLY
PRETTY THERE.
请不要告诉她我告诉过你，好吗？
PLEASE DON'T TELL HER
I TOLD YOU, OKAY?
嘿，我守口如瓶。
HEY, MY LIPS ARE SEALED.
戴尔：用缝合线横向准备。
Dale:
PREPARE TRANSVERSELY
WITH RUNNING VICRYL.
三-O。
THREE-OH.
先生们，这是你们活检的结果。
GENTLEMEN, I HAVE
THE RESULTS OF
YOUR BIOPSY.
你们猜猜我们在显微镜下看到了什么？
CARE TO GUESS WHAT WE SAW
UNDER THE MICROSCOPE?
肯定是霍奇金淋巴瘤。
GOT TO BE
HODGKIN'S.
不。
NO.
转移性腺癌？
METASTATIC
ADENO?
又错了。
WRONG AGAIN.
生精小管。
SEMINIFEROUS TUBULES.
什么？
WHAT?
你在开玩笑吧？
YOU'RE KIDDING?
你活检了两个睾丸。
YOU BIOPSIED
TWO TESTICLES.
看来芭比是个男孩。
IT SEEMS THAT BARBIE IS A BOY.
谁知道有这么多关于肠道的书籍？
WHO KNEW THERE WERE SO
MANY TEXTS ON THE BOWELS?
是啊。这只是我能找到的。
YEAH. THIS IS JUST
WHAT I COULD GET
MY HANDS ON.
我想，所有这些强烈的兴趣……
I SUPPOSE WITH ALL
THIS INTENSE INTEREST...
（吵闹的派对声音）
( raucous party sounds )
意味着我们的肠道在未来很多年都得到很好的照顾。
MEANS OUR BOWELS ARE
IN GOOD HANDS FOR
MANY YEARS TO COME.
真是个好想法。
THAT'S A NICE THOUGHT.
嘿，听起来派对已经开始了。
HEY, SOUNDS LIKE THE
PARTY'S UP AND RUNNING.
男声：派对！
Man:
PARTY!
是啊！
YEAH!
（欢呼声和叫喊声）
( hooting and hollering )
（欢呼声和笑声）
( whooping and laughing )
卡特医生。
DR. CARTER.
就在那里。
RIGHT THERE.
瞄得真准，老兄。
NICE AIM, DUDE.
你差点用那个灭了火。
YOU ALMOST PUT OUT
THE FIRE WITH THAT ONE.
嘿，卡特医生！
HEY, DR. CARTER!
（音乐停止）
( music stops )
（所有人呻吟）
( all groaning )
好了，孩子们，派对结束了。
OKAY, KIDS,
PARTY'S OVER.
你们不必回家
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO HOME
但你们不能留在这里。
BUT YOU CAN'T STAY HERE.
怎么了？我们太吵了吗？
WHAT'S UP? WERE WE TOO LOUD?
不，是家具着火了。
NO, THE FURNITURE
WAS TOO ON FIRE.
真的吗？对不起。
REALLY? I'M SORRY.
我会在我房间里学习的。
I'LL BE IN MY ROOM, STUDYING.
万圣节快乐。
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
她又对我这样。
SHE DID IT TO ME AGAIN.
她正在办理托管
SHE'S IN ESCROW
我是从瑞秋那里听说的。
AND I HAD TO HEAR ABOUT IT
FROM RACHEL.
也许她今晚想告诉你。
MAYBE SHE WAS GOING
TO TELL YOU TONIGHT.
也许吧。或者她只是打算
MAYBE. OR MAYBE
SHE WAS JUST GOING
给我寄张圣路易斯的明信片。
TO SEND ME A POSTCARD
FROM ST. LOUIS.
你和瑞秋相处得真的很好，是吗？
YOU REALLY HAD A GOOD TIME
WITH RACHEL, DIDN'T YOU?
是啊。是啊，我很好。
YEAH. YEAH, I DID.
查塔洛夫斯基的戒毒搜索进行得怎么样了？
HOW'S CHATTAROWSKI'S
DETOX SEARCH GOING?
四东区没床位了
THEY WERE ALL OUT OF
BEDS IN FOUR EAST
但我坚持住了
BUT I STOOD MY GROUND
坚持说他是一个很好的戒毒候选人
AND INSISTED THAT HE WAS
A GOOD DETOX CANDIDATE
最后，他们让步了
AND FINALLY,
THEY CAVED IN
给了他一个四西区的床位。
AND GAVE HIM A PLACE
ON FOUR WEST.
哇。你肯定欠他们一些人情。
WOW. YOU MUST OWE
THEM SOME FAVORS.
几个，但值得。
A COUPLE,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
嗯，你试过了，你知道吗？
WELL, YOU TRIED, YOU KNOW?
戴尔：当我们探查腹膜后时
Dale:
WHEN WE EXPLORED
THE RETROPERITINEUM
我们发现了
WE DISCOVERED
两个小肿块。
TWO SMALL MASSES.
肿块。什么肿块？
MASSES. WHAT
KIND OF MASSES?
我们也担心
WE WERE
CONCERNED, TOO
所以我们送去了一份活检的冰冻切片
SO WE SENT DOWN
A FROZEN SECTION
OF THE BIOPSY
结果显示是睾丸组织。
THAT REVEALED
TESTICULAR TISSUE.
那是什么意思？
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
芭比有一种病
BARBIE HAS A CONDITION
叫做睾丸女性化。
CALLED TESTICULAR
FEMINIZATION.
从基因上讲，她是一个男性
GENETICALLY,
SHE'S A MALE
有X-Y染色体
WITH X-Y
CHROMOSOMES
但在发育过程中
BUT DURING DEVELOPMENT
胎儿组织对睾丸激素有抵抗力
THE FETAL TISSUE WAS
RESISTANT TO TESTOSTERONE
外部生殖器
AND THE
EXTERNAL
GENITALIA
发育成了女性。
DEVELOPED
AS FEMALE.
一定有哪里搞错了。
THERE'S GOT TO
BE A MISTAKE.
没有错。
NO MISTAKE.
阴道只不过是一个盲袋——
THE VAGINA'S NOTHING
BUT A BLIND POUCH--
没有子宫也没有卵巢。
NO UTERUS
NOR OVARIES.
她需要接受雌激素替代疗法。
SHE'LL NEED TO BE ON
ESTROGEN REPLACEMENT THERAPY.
我的小女孩有睾丸。
MY LITTLE GIRL
HAS TESTICLES.
事实上，我们不得不切除它们
ACTUALLY, WE HAD
TO REMOVE THEM
因为恶性转化的发生率很高。
BECAUSE OF THE HIGH INCIDENCE
OF MALIGNANT TRANSFORMATION.
我……我不明白。
I-I-I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
我……我给她换过尿布。
I... I CHANGED HER DIAPERS.
我了解她的每一寸。
I KNOW EVERY INCH
OF HER.
她是个男孩？
SHE'S A BOY?
基因不重要。
THE GENETICS
DON'T MATTER.
你把她当作女孩抚养。
YOU'VE RAISED HER
AS A GIRL.
芭比是女孩。
BARBIE IS A GIRL.
她看起来就是这样。
IT'S WHAT SHE
LOOKS LIKE.
那是她的身份。
IT'S HER
IDENTITY.
什么都改变不了。
NOTHING WILL CHANGE THAT.
但你必须明白，她永远不会来月经
BUT YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT SHE'LL NEVER MENSTRUATE
或生育孩子。
OR BEAR
CHILDREN.
（压抑的抽泣）
( stifled sob )
（轻声抽泣）
( sobbing softly )
显然，这让人震惊。
OBVIOUSLY,
THIS HAS COME AS A SHOCK.
你需要时间来适应。
YOU'LL NEED TIME TO ADJUST.
芭比正在康复。
BARBIE'S
RECOVERING.
我们会把你转介给一个遗传咨询师。
WE'LL REFER YOU
TO A GENETIC COUNSELOR.
他们会帮你决定何时以及如何告诉她。
THEY'LL HELP YOU DECIDE
WHEN AND HOW TO TELL HER.
谢谢你，医生。
THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
干得漂亮。
NICE JOB.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
当然，你忘了提
OF COURSE, YOU
FORGOT TO MENTION
他们得把芭比的名字改成肯。
THEY'LL HAVE TO
CHANGE BARBIE'S
NAME TO KEN.
我今天过得这么糟，随便来吧。
AFTER THE DAY I'VE HAD,
JUST LINE THEM UP.
说的没错。你就得这么干，伙计。
WORD. THAT'S HOW YOU
GOT TO DO IT, MAN.
努力工作，尽情玩乐。
WORK HARD, PLAY HARD.
我活该尽情玩乐。
I DESERVE
TO PLAY HARD.
我必须检查所有这些粪便样本
I HAD TO CHECK
ALL THOSE STOOL SAMPLES
看有没有粪便白细胞，老兄。
FOR FECAL LEUKOCYTES, DUDE.
你觉得那很糟糕吗？
YOU THINK THAT'S BAD?
我的住院医让我给这些流浪汉
MY RESIDENT
HAD ME GIVE PHYSICAL EXAMS
做体格检查。
TO THESE HOMELESS SHELTER GUYS.
有一个人的脓肿上爬满了蛆。
ONE HAD MAGGOTS
CRAWLING ALL OVER AN ABSCESS.
（呻吟）
( groaning )
至少你的住院医承认你的存在。
AT LEAST YOUR RESIDENTS
ACKNOWLEDGE YOUR EXISTENCE.
我的甚至都不知道我在这里。
MINE DON'T EVEN KNOW
I'M HERE.
我从这只橡胶手臂上得到的尊重都比这多。
I GET MORE RESPECT
FROM THIS RUBBER ARM.
（欢呼声和笑声）
( whooping and laughing )
如果我们有那把锯子，我们可能就救了这个人。
WE MIGHT HAVE SAVED THIS GUY
IF WE HAD THE SAW.
我们可以在两秒钟内切开胸骨
WE COULD HAVE CUT ACROSS
THE STERNUM IN TWO SECONDS
而不是凿了将近一分钟。
INSTEAD OF CHISELING
FOR CLOSE TO A MINUTE.
凯瑞，那家伙已经死了。
KERRY, THE
GUY WAS DEAD.
再多几秒钟也救不活他。
ANOTHER FEW SECONDS
WOULDN'T HAVE BROUGHT
HIM BACK TO LIFE.
但这会给他一个机会。
BUT IT WOULD'VE GIVEN HIM
A CHANCE.
我们不会浪费时间和金钱
WE ARE NOT GOING
TO WASTE TIME AND MONEY
在急诊室医生身上训练手术器械
TRAINING E.R. DOCS ON
SURGICAL EQUIPMENT
这种器械一年只用一次。
THAT WILL GET USED
ONCE A YEAR.
但如果我们有锯子
BUT IF WE HAD THE SAW
我们可以对所有伴有心脏骤停的穿透性胸部创伤
WE COULD GIVE
MIDLINE THORACOTOMIES
进行正中开胸术。
FOR ALL PENETRATING CHEST TRAUMA
WITH FULL ARREST.
但这不符合医疗护理标准。
BUT THAT IS NOT
THE STANDARD OF CARE.
医疗护理标准的结果很糟糕。
THE STANDARD OF CARE
GIVES MISERABLE RESULTS.
如果在救护车上心脏骤停，10%存活。
IF THEY ARREST IN THE AMBULANCE,
TEN PERCENT SURVIVE.
如果在急诊室心脏骤停，30%存活。
IF THEY ARREST IN THE E.R.,
30% SURVIVE.
我认为正中开胸术
I THINK
MIDLINE THORACOTOMY
能更好地暴露以修复心脏损伤。
GIVES US BETTER EXPOSURE
TO REPAIR CARDIAC INJURIES.
凯瑞，如果你对此如此感兴趣
KERRY, IF YOU'RE
SO DAMNED INTERESTED IN THIS
你为什么不做个研究呢？
WHY DON'T YOU DO A STUDY?
好的，我会的。
ALL RIGHT, I WILL.
好。我完全知道外科的哪个家伙
GOOD. I KNOW EXACTLY
THE GUY FROM SURGERY
可以和你协调。彼得？
TO COORDINATE WITH YOU.
PETER?
凯瑞和我刚才正在讨论一项联合研究
KERRY AND I WERE JUST
DISCUSSING A JOINT STUDY
急诊室和外科之间的。
BETWEEN THE E.R.
AND SURGERY.
外侧开胸与正中开胸
LATERAL VERSUS
MIDLINE THORACOTOMY
治疗伴有心脏骤停的穿透性胸部创伤。
FOR PENETRATING
CHEST TRAUMA
WITH FULL ARREST.
是因为今天早上吗？
IS THIS
BECAUSE OF THIS MORNING?
凯瑞，你为什么不起草一份提案，包括预算
KERRY, WHY DON'T YOU DRAW UP
A PROPOSAL, INCLUDING A BUDGET
并在接下来的两周内交到我桌上？
AND HAVE IT ON MY DESK
IN THE NEXT TWO WEEKS?
听着，我不认为急诊室医生
LISTEN, I DON'T
THINK E.R. DOCS
应该玩胸骨锯。
SHOULD BE PLAYING
AROUND WITH A STERNAL SAW.
我也不。
NEITHER DO I.
那为什么你支持她？
WELL, THEN,
WHY DID YOU
SUPPORT HER?
我没有。我只是让她白费力气。
I'M NOT. I'M LETTING HER
SPIN HER WHEELS.
她会写一份提案，而这份提案
SHE'LL WRITE A PROPOSAL,
AND IT WON'T MAKE IT
在人类受试者委员会那里
THROUGH THE HUMAN
SUBJECTS COMMITTEE
一百万年也通不过。
IN ABOUT A
MILLION YEARS.
M&M？
M & M?
哦，不，不。
OH, NO, NO.
嘿。哦！
HEY.
OH!
听着，我预订了邓普西餐厅，10点。
LISTEN, I MADE RESERVATIONS
AT DEMPSEY'S FOR 10:00.
彼得，我不知道。
PETER, I DON'T KNOW.
我忙得不可开交。
I'M PRETTY SWAMPED.
你在说什么？
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
今天是万圣节。
IT'S HALLOWEEN.
但邓普西餐厅不太有万圣节气氛。
BUT DEMPSEY'S
ISN'T REALLY
HALLOWEEN-Y.
你知道，它会一直这样。
YOU KNOW,
IT'LL KEEP.
（叹气）
( sighing )
嘿，沃尔特，怎么了，伙计？是我。
HEY, WALT, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
IT'S ME.
听着，我，呃，我需要你帮个忙。
LISTEN, I, UH,
I NEED TO ASK YOU A FAVOR.
看到这个了吗？
SEE THIS ONE?
那是蓝骑士。
THAT'S THE BLUE RIDER.
好吧，“可爱”的牛仔。
ALL RIGHT, THE
"CUTE" COWBOY.
爸！
DAD!
瑞秋，我没听错你的点单吧？
RACH, DID I HEAR
YOUR ORDER RIGHT?
你讨厌大黄和核桃。
YOU HATE RHUBARB
AND WALNUTS.
我现在喜欢了。
I LIKE IT NOW.
爸爸做的派很好吃。
DAD MAKES GOOD PIE.
他一直都这样。
HE ALWAYS DID.
珍，你是不是想讨好我？
JEN, YOU TRYING
TO BUTTER ME UP?
不，我只是记得
NO, I JUST REMEMBER
你妈妈著名的大黄派食谱。
YOUR MOM'S FAMOUS
RHUBARB PIE RECIPE.
抱歉你感冒了还要加班。
SORRY YOU HAVE TO WORK LATE
WITH A COLD.
你还撑得住吗？
ARE YOU HOLDING UP?
是啊，只是我的鼻窦。
YEAH, IT'S JUST
MY SINUSES.
瑞秋，你为什么不去洗手？
RACHEL, WHY DON'T YOU
GO WASH YOUR HANDS?
好的。
OKAY.
圣路易斯，嗯？
ST. LOUIS, HUH?
她告诉你了。
SHE TOLD YOU.
说漏嘴了。
IT SLIPPED OUT.
那是个很棒的工作，马克。
IT'S A GREAT JOB,
MARK.
学校一流，而且……
THE SCHOOLS
ARE TOP RATE, AND...
听起来不错。
IT SOUNDS GOOD.
我本来准备打一架。
I WAS READY FOR A FIGHT.
我想我们这辈子已经吵够了
I THINK WE'VE DONE
ENOUGH FIGHTING
FOR A LIFETIME
你不觉得吗？
DON'T YOU THINK?
是啊。
YEAH.
在一个完美的世界里
IN A PERFECT WORLD
我们都可以一年365天都陪着她
WE COULD BOTH SPEND
365 DAYS A YEAR WITH HER
但我们不能。
BUT WE CAN'T.
圣路易斯不远。
ST. LOUIS ISN'T VERY FAR.
不。
NO.
我会有假期和暑假。
I'LL HAVE HOLIDAYS
AND SUMMERS.
这个夏天和她在一起
SPENDING THIS TIME WITH
HER THIS SUMMER HAS...
让我……
MADE ME THINK ABOUT HOW...
让我想起我们花太多时间思考自己了。
WE SPENT WAY TOO MUCH TIME
THINKING ABOUT OURSELVES.
她告诉我你们相处得很好。
SHE TOLD ME YOU GUYS
GOT ALONG REALLY WELL.
是啊。
YEAH.
是啊，那，呃……
YEAH, IT WAS, UH...
那很有趣。
IT WAS A LOT OF...
IT WAS A LOT OF FUN.
谢谢你。
THANK YOU.
现在还是万圣节吗？
IS IT STILL
HALLOWEEN?
呃……是的。
UH... YES.
你还有几个小时。
YOU HAVE A FEW
MORE HOURS LEFT.
我想我不能
I GUESS I
WON'T BE ABLE
去要糖了。
TO GO TRICK-OR-TREATING.
今年不行。
NOT THIS YEAR.
对不起。
I'M SORRY.
有一天，嗯？
SOME DAY, HUH?
没关系。
THAT'S OKAY.
反正最好玩的部分是做服装。
THE BEST PART WAS MAKING
THE COSTUME, ANYWAY.
我和妈妈一起做的。
ME AND MY MOM
MADE IT TOGETHER.
你还留着我的头冠吗？
DO YOU STILL HAVE MY TIARA?
呃……
UH...
是的。
YES.
是的，就在这里。
YES, RIGHT HERE.
等等，我来弄。
WAIT, LET ME DO THAT.
好了。
THERE.
我看起来怎么样？
HOW DO I LOOK?
哦！像个美丽的仙女公主。
OH! LIKE A BEAUTIFUL
FAIRY PRINCESS.
（笑）
( laughing )
不！
NO!
喝吧，伙计！
DRINK UP, BUDDY!
有些人酒量不行。
SOME PEOPLE
CANNOT HOLD THEIR LIQUOR.
我们应该彻底捉弄他。
WE SHOULD TOTALLY
MESS WITH HIS MIND.
哦，你是说热水泡手那个把戏吗？
OH, YOU MEAN THE-HAND-
IN-THE-WARM-WATER TRICK?
别在沙发上，露西。
NOT ON THE COUCH,
LUCY.
来吧。
COME ON.
我来。
I GOT IT.
（笑）：住手！
( laughing ):
STOP IT!
你觉得他没事吗？
DO YOU THINK HE'S OKAY?
是啊，他只是个酒量小的
YEAH, HE'S JUST
A LIGHTWEIGHT
就这样。
THAT'S ALL.
他脉搏强劲，还在呼吸。
HE HAS A STRONG PULSE,
AND HE'S STILL BREATHING.
你在急诊室待太久了。
YOU'VE BEEN
IN THE E.R.
WAY TOO LONG.
让我们把派对搞起来！
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED
RIGHT!
你要给他剃头吗？
YOU GOING TO
SHAVE HIS HEAD?
不，那会很
NO, THAT
WOULD BE
残忍和不寻常。
CRUEL AND UNUSUAL.
这很卑鄙！
THIS IS MEAN!
这很卑鄙。
THIS IS MEAN.
你还没见过呢。
YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHIN' YET.
嗯，即使他醉了，那也应该管用。
WELL, EVEN IF HE WAS DRUNK,
THAT SHOULD STILL WORK.
不，停，停，停。
NO, STOP, STOP, STOP.
等等，等等，等等。威利？
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
WILLIE?
威利，醒醒！
WILLIE, WAKE UP!
有人需要打911
SOMEONE NEEDS
TO CALL 911
然后去找卡特。
AND GO GET CARTER.
现实点吧，露丝。
GET REAL, LUCE.
如果我们叫卡特医生，他会告发我们的。
IF WE CALL DR. CARTER,
HE'LL NARC.
不，威利有麻烦了。
NO, WILLIE'S
IN TROUBLE.
我们需要做点什么。
WE NEED
TO DO SOMETHING.
不，露丝，伯尼是对的。
NO, LUCE,
BERNIE'S RIGHT.
我们是医学生。
WE'RE MED STUDENTS.
我们能搞定。
WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
这不是课堂。
THIS IS NOT CLASS.
这是我们的朋友。
THIS IS OUR FRIEND.
现在，你们打911。
NOW, YOU GUYS
CALL 911.
我要去找卡特。
I'M GOING
TO GO GET CARTER.
卡特医生？！
DR. CARTER?!
卡特医生，醒醒！
WAKE UP, DR. CARTER!
醒醒！
WAKE UP!
好的，大家，退后。给他点空气。
OKAY, EVERYBODY, BACK OFF.
GIVE HIM SOME AIR.
有人打911了吗？
ANYBODY CALL 911?
我打了，卡特医生。
I DID, DR. CARTER.
来吧，威利，醒醒。
COME ON, WILLIE, WAKE UP.
醒醒！
WAKE UP!
我颈动脉搏动微弱，但他没有呼吸。
I GOT A WEAK CAROTID PULSE,
BUT HE'S NOT BREATHING.
哦，天哪。
OH, MAN.
（喘气）
( puffing )
（呕吐）
( retching )
（所有人呻吟）
( all groaning )
哦，恶心！
OH, GROSS!
我能做点什么吗？我能做点什么？
CAN I DO ANYTHING?
WHAT CAN I DO?
他吐了。那……那很好，对吧？
HE VOMITED. THAT'S A...
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
不，那很糟糕。
NO, THAT'S BAD.
如果他呕吐
IF HE VOMITS
呕吐物进入肺部
AND IT GETS DOWN
IN HIS LUNGS
他可能会死于吸入性肺炎。
HE COULD DIE
OF ASPIRATION PNEUMONIA.
呃，他父母住在唐纳斯格罗夫。
UH, HIS PARENTS LIVE
IN DOWNER'S GROVE.
打电话给他们。给他们打电话。
CALL THEM.
GIVE THEM A CALL.
我们在这儿，二楼！
WE'RE UP HERE, SECOND FLOOR!
“E-X”——那是什么？
"E-X"-- WHAT'S THAT?
那是液体迷魂药。
THAT'S LIQUID ECSTASY.
那是什么？
WHAT IS THAT?
像一种麻醉剂。
IT'S LIKE A NARCOTIC.
还有其他人服用吗？！
DID ANYBODY ELSE TAKE IT?!
我不知道威利服用了。布兰奇也服用了。
I DIDN'T KNOW
WILLIE TOOK IT.
BRANCH TOOK SOME.
我不能离开威利。
I CAN'T LEAVE WILLIE.
我去。
I'LL GO.
很干净。他们重放了一百万次。
IT WAS CLEAN. THEY SHOWED
THE REPLAY A MILLION TIMES.
拜托！他们越位得太离谱了。
PLEASE! IT WAS A JOKE
HOW OFFSIDES THEY WERE.
你在做梦。付钱吧。
YOU'RE DREAMING. PAY UP.
马克，那是幸运酒铺。
MARK, THAT WAS
LUCKY LIQUOR.
啊，流浪汉最好的朋友。
AH, A VAGRANT'S BEST FRIEND.
他们说有一个穿着县医院病号服的家伙
THEY SAY THEY HAVE A GUY
IN A COUNTY PATIENT GOWN
拿着一个黄色静脉输液袋，试图买啤酒。
WITH A YELLOW I.V. BAG
TRYING TO BUY BEER.
“不穿衬衫
WHAT EVER HAPPENED
TO "NO SHIRT
不穿鞋，不服务”是怎么回事？
NO SHOES, NO SERVICE"?
他们想拖住他
THEY'RE TRYING
TO STALL HIM
直到有人来
UNTIL SOMEONE COMES
但他们不会等一整天。
BUT THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO HANG ON ALL DAY.
告诉你吧。嘿，格拉巴斯基。
TELL YOU WHAT.
HEY, GRABARSKY.
你下去把他接上来，我们就扯平了。
YOU GO DOWN AND PICK THIS
GUY UP AND WE'RE EVEN.
听起来怎么样？
HOW'S THAT SOUND?
这个醉汉是朋友吗？
THIS DRUNK A FRIEND?
不，但他欠我的比你多。
NO, BUT HE OWES ME
BIGGER THAN YOU DO.
把他当做入院病人。
CONSIDER HIM ADMITTED.
他在哪？他室友说他去洗澡了。
WHERE IS HE?
HIS ROOMMATE SAID
HE WENT TO TAKE A SHOWER.
威利怎么样？医护人员给他插管了。
HOW'S WILLIE?
PARAMEDICS
INTUBATED HIM.
液体迷魂药。
LIQUID ECSTASY.
这些家伙是医学生。
THESE GUYS ARE
MED STUDENTS.
你以为他们会更懂事。
YOU THINK THEY'D
KNOW BETTER.
是的，你会的。
YEAH, YOU WOULD.
布兰奇？
BRANCH?
布兰奇！
BRANCH!
（呻吟）
( groans )
（水声停止）
( water stops )
布兰奇，醒醒！醒醒！
BRANCH, WAKE UP!
WAKE UP!
我们把他弄出去。
LET'S GET HIM
OUT OF HERE.
不，他没有呼吸。
NO, HE'S NOT
MOVING ANY AIR.
没有脉搏。
NO PULSE.
该死！
DAMN IT!
我来做胸外按压。
I'LL START
CHEST COMPRESSIONS.
注射器在哪里？
WHERE'S THE SYRINGE?
我告诉你。
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
去找医护人员。我来做心肺复苏。
GO FIND THE PARAMEDICS.
I'LL DO CPR.
好的。
OKAY.
卢宾先生的体温刚刚升到101.4度。
MR. LUBIN JUST SPIKED
TO 101.4.
去做一个发热检查。
GO AHEAD AND DRAW
A FEVER WORKUP.
抽一管Setzer，在11点给药后
DRAW A SETZER FOR A PRE AND
POST-GENTAMICIN LEVEL
做一次庆大霉素的前后水平检查。
WITH THE 11:00 DOSE.
嘿，怎么样？
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
我们似乎很忙。
WE SEEM TO BE
RATHER BUSY.
我有一个很棒的小实习生在帮我。
I'VE GOT A GREAT LITTLE
INTERN HELPING ME OUT.
戴尔，听着，嗯……
DALE, LISTEN, UM...
现在是10点半了，你甚至还没开始
IT'S 10:30 AND
YOU'RE NOT EVEN ON
所以把那些琐事交接出去。
SO SIGN OUT THE SCUT.
那就是值班团队的工作……
THAT'S WHAT THE
ON-CALL TEAM IS FOR...
除非你有什么问题。
UNLESS YOU HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
没关系。
THAT'S FINE.
你准备好了吗？
YOU READY?
给我十分钟
GIVE ME TEN MINUTES
换回我的服装。
TO GET BACK
INTO MY COSTUME.
天啊。你真的要穿那个东西，是吧？
GOD. YOU'RE REALLY GOING
TO WEAR THAT THING, HUH?
当然。
OF COURSE.
好的。听着，等你准备好了
OKAY. LISTEN,
WHEN YOU'RE READY
我会在前面，好吗？
I'LL BE OUT FRONT, OKAY?
就告诉我你想成为一名航空公司飞行员。
JUST TELL ME YOU WANTED
TO BE AN AIRLINE PILOT.
哦，拜托。我甚至不喜欢
OH, PLEASE.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE
坐小飞机去克利夫兰。
TAKING A PUDDLE JUMPER
TO CLEVELAND.
快点。
HURRY UP.
这是警察骚扰！
THIS IS POLICE HARASSMENT!
记住罗德尼·金！
REMEMBER RODNEY KING!
G医生，这是你要的人。
DR. G., HERE'S YOUR MAN.
他反抗得很厉害。
HE PUT UP QUITE A FIGHT.
说什么万圣节，
TALKING ABOUT IT'S HALLOWEEN
他只是在玩角色扮演。
AND HOW HE'S JUST
PLAYING DRESS-UP.
我就是！
I AM!
格拉巴斯基，你抓错人了。
GRABARSKY,
THAT'S THE WRONG GUY.
幸运酒铺，穿着医院病号服的大个子。
LUCKY LIQUOR, BIG GUY
IN A HOSPITAL GOWN.
他有点像，呃……
HE KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE, UH...
杰瑞！
JERRY!
劳埃德。
LLOYD.
你在这里做什么？
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
劳埃德是谁？
WHO'S LLOYD?
我是那个笨蛋的表弟。
I'M THAT
KNUCKLEHEAD'S COUSIN.
谁知道他们能连续两次中
WHO KNEW THEY COULD HIT
基因彩票？
THE GENETIC
POWERBALL TWICE?
杰瑞……
JERRY...
嗯……你看，他需要一件服装
WELL... SEE,
HE NEEDED A COSTUME
而且麋鹿兄弟会有个大比赛……
AND THERE'S A BIG CONTEST
AT THE ELKS LODGE...
我得了荣誉奖，表弟。
I WON
AN HONORABLE MENTION, CUZ.
恭喜。
CONGRATULATIONS.
（笑）
( laughing )
还需要什么吗，道格？
NEED ANYTHING
ELSE, DOUG?
除了一个48小时的工作日？
OTHER THAN A 48-HOUR DAY?
我要下班了。明天一早见。
I'M GOING TO TAKE OFF.
SEE YOU BRIGHT AND EARLY.
嗯，明天一早。
MMM, BRIGHT
AND EARLY.
是的。
YEP.
嘿，道格，你今天干得不错。
HEY, DOUG, YOU DID
A NICE JOB TODAY.
对于一个新手主治医生来说还不错。
NOT BAD FOR A
ROOKIE ATTENDING.
嗯，看看你处理这些怎么样。
WELL, LET'S SEE HOW
YOU DO WITH THESE.
那是什么？
WHAT'S THAT?
我们在主急诊室
THE OVERFLOW CHARTS
看过的儿科病人的溢出病历。
FOR THE PEDIATRIC PATIENTS
WE SAW IN THE MAIN E.R.
根据政策
ACCORDING TO POLICY
你需要批准它们。
YOU NEED
TO SIGN OFF ON THEM.
（轻声笑）
( slight chuckle )
你很享受这个，是吧？
YOU'RE LOVING THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
是啊。这个儿科急诊室也没那么糟糕。
YEAH. THIS PEDES E.R. ISN'T
SUCH A BAD IDEA AFTER ALL.
万圣节快乐，菜鸟。
HAPPY HALLOWEEN, ROOKIE.
布兰奇·克罗克特和威利·戈德曼，22岁和23岁。
BRANCH CROCKETT AND WILLIE
GOLDMAN, AGES 22 AND 23.
酒精和GHB混合过量。
MIXED OVERDOSE
OF ALCOHOL AND GHB.
威利因呼吸骤停插管。
WILLIE'S INTUBATED
FROM A RESPIRATORY ARREST.
布兰奇因肺动脉骤停后使用肾上腺素复苏。
BRANCH CAME BACK WITH EPI
AFTER A PULMONARY ARREST.
怎么了，是深夜泡吧吗？
WHAT, A LITTLE
LATE-NIGHT CLUB-HOPPING?
不，医学院万圣节派对。
NO, MED SCHOOL
HALLOWEEN PARTY.
嗯。
HMM.
好了，大家，数我的数。
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
ON MY COUNT.
一，二，三。
ONE, TWO, THREE.
血常规，血气分析，电解质，血液酒精浓度
C.B.C., A.B.G.,
LYTES, BLOOD ALCOHOL
毒理筛查和12导联心电图。
TOX SCREEN AND A 12-LEAD.
斯蒂芬妮，打电话给呼吸科
STEPHANIE, CALL RESPIRATORY
要一台呼吸机。
FOR A VENT.
有人应该给他父母打电话。
SOMEONE SHOULD
CALL HIS PARENTS.
露西可以做。我想帮忙。
LUCY CAN DO THAT.
I WANT TO HELP.
你醉了。
YOU'RE DRUNK.
你不该在这里。
YOU DON'T
BELONG IN HERE.
现在出去。
NOW GET OUT.
彼得
PETER
你完全疯了吗？
HAVE YOU GONE
COMPLETELY BALMY?
（笑）
( laughing )
只是玩得疯。
JUST GETTING FUNKY.
（笑）
( laughs )
嘿，认识一下我的侄子，花生。
HEY, MEET
MY NEPHEW, PEANUT.
很高兴见到你。
NICE TO MEET YOU.
你好。
HELLO.
是坐干草车！
IT'S A HAY RIDE!
是的，是坐干草车。
YES, IT'S
A HAY RIDE.
那么，彼得叔叔，去哪里？
SO, WHERE TO,
UNCLE PETE?
密歇根大道。
MICHIGAN AVE.
嘿，把那八轨磁带放进去。
HEY, POP THAT
EIGHT-TRACK IN.
稳当。
SOLID.
你不明白。
YOU DON'T GET IT.
你从来没猜到我小时候想成为谁。
YOU NEVER FIGURED OUT
WHO I WANTED TO BE AS A KID.
（《肖申克》主题曲响起）
( Shaft theme playing )
哦，我的天啊！
OH, MY GOD!
沙夫特。
SHAFT.
（轻笑）
( chuckles )
约翰·沙夫特。
JOHN SHAFT.
（两人笑）
( both laughing )
嘿，韦弗医生。
HEY, DR. WEAVER.
要去享受万圣节之夜吗？
OFF TO ENJOY
ALL HALLOW'S EVE?
实际上，是的。
ACTUALLY, I AM.
我只是想把这个账单给你。
I JUST WANTED
TO GIVE YOU THIS BILL.
289美元？
$289?
是啊，你运气好
YEAH, YOU'RE LUCKY
轮椅没有损坏。
THE WHEELCHAIR
CAME BACK UNDAMAGED.
情况可能会糟糕得多。
IT COULD HAVE BEEN
A LOT WORSE.
韦弗医生，我没有300块钱。
DR. WEAVER, I DON'T
HAVE 300 BUCKS.
嗯，所以我安排了
WELL, THAT'S WHY
I'VE ARRANGED
从你工资里扣。
TO HAVE IT TAKEN
OUT OF YOUR PAYCHECK.
每周28.90美元，持续十周。
$28.90 A WEEK
FOR THE NEXT TEN WEEKS.
那会一直持续到假日购物季。
THAT'LL RUN RIGHT INTO
THE HOLIDAY BUYING SEASON.
凯瑞，你有一秒钟吗？
KERRY, YOU GOT
A SECOND?
是啊，怎么了？
YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
呃，我想给你提个醒
UH, I WANT TO GIVE YOU
A HEAD'S UP
关于委员会投票。
ON THE COMMITTEE VOTE.
那不应该明天早上
THAT'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE ANNOUNCED
才公布。
UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING.
嗯，他们已经统计完了
WELL, THEY'VE
TALLIED IT ALREADY
他们投票给了利特瓦克。
AND THEY VOTED
FOR LITVAK.
哦。
OH.
他们得把办公室门加宽
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WIDEN THE OFFICE DOOR
才能容下他膨胀的脑袋。
FOR HIS SWOLLEN HEAD.
是啊，他有点混蛋，是吧？
YEAH, HE'S KIND OF
AN ASS, ISN'T HE?
嗯，如果这有什么意义的话，我投了你一票。
WELL, IF IT MEANS ANYTHING,
I VOTED FOR YOU.
谢谢，马克。
THANKS, MARK.
这笔钱从哪一个工资单开始生效？
WHICH PAYCHECK
DOES THIS BECOME EFFECTIVE?
你知道吗？
YOU KNOW WHAT?
不生效。
IT DOESN'T.
你是认真的吗？
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
我是认真的。
I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
给你表弟一个轮椅。
GIVE YOUR COUSIN
A WHEELCHAIR.
给你老姑妈一个快速输液器。
GIVE YOUR MAIDEN AUNT
A RAPID INFUSER.
我不在乎。
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN.
你对这个太痴迷了。
YOU'RE GETTING OBSESSIVE
OVER THIS.
我刚才给了你血管穿刺针吗？
DID I JUST HAND
YOU ANGIOCATHS?
是的，一打。
YEAH, A GROSS.
一打是多少？
WHAT'S A GROSS?
144个，你给了。
144, AND YOU DID.
你听我说话了吗？
ARE YOU LISTENING
TO ME?
是的，我在听。
YES, I AM.
光工作不玩耍，道格会变傻。
ALL WORK AND NO PLAY
MAKES DOUG A DULL BOY.
现在，看这个。
NOW, LOOK AT THIS.
我刚订了三箱口服补液盐。
I JUST ORDERED THREE
CASES OF PEDIALYTE.
这是口服唑。
THIS IS PEDIAZOLE.
这一定是……哎哟！哦……
THIS HAS GOT TO BE...
OW! OH...
道格，你没事吧？
DOUG,
YOU ALL RIGHT?
哦，我的天啊！抓住它！抓住它！
OH, MY GOD!
HOLD IT! HOLD IT!
按住它！
PUT PRESSURE ON IT!
（假装呻吟）
( fake moans )
你个混蛋。
YOU BASTARD.
你做得出来，却受不了，是吧？
YOU CAN DISH IT OUT,
YOU CAN'T TAKE IT, HUH?
哦，你……报复真是个贱人，是吧？
OH, YOU...
PAYBACK IS A
BITCH, ISN'T IT?
你真差劲。离我远点。你真差劲。
YOU SUCK. GET AWAY
FROM ME. YOU SUCK.
晚上好。我想吸你的血。
GOOD EVENING. I WANT
TO SUCK YOUR BLOOD.
不，我不是……不，不。我不亲回去。
NO, I'M NOT... NO, NO.
I'M NOT KISSING BACK.
（轻笑）
( chuckles )
（叹气）
( sighs )
嘿，卡特医生。
HEY, DR. CARTER.
露西。
LUCY.
他们怎么样了？
HOW ARE THEY?
他们会没事的。
THEY'LL BE FINE.
我不知道发生了什么。
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
前一秒，我们还在闲逛
ONE SECOND, WE
WERE HANGING OUT
下一秒……
AND THE NEXT...
发生的事情是
WHAT HAPPENED WAS
你的两个同学今晚差点死了。
TWO OF YOUR CLASSMATES
ALMOST DIED TONIGHT.
我不知道他们在使用GHB。
I DIDN'T KNOW THEY
WERE DOING GHB.
嗯，你是派对的负责人。
WELL, YOU WERE IN CHARGE
OF THE PARTY.
当事情失控时，我制止了它。
I BROKE IT UP WHEN
THINGS GOT OUT OF HAND.
YOU CONTINUED TO PARTY.
两个人被担架抬了出去。
TWO GUYS ROLLED OUT OF HERE
ON GURNEYS.
呃……我错过了什么吗？
UH... DID I MISS ANYTHING?
关于我不能管束所有人的部分……
THE PART ABOUT ME NOT BEING ABLE
TO POLICE EVERYONE...
还有你是宿舍辅导员
AND THE PART ABOUT YOU BEING
THE RESIDENT ADVISOR
和负责人。
AND THE ONE IN CHARGE.
你说的对，露西。
YOU'RE RIGHT, LUCY.
你知道吗？我是负责人
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M IN CHARGE
我以为你足够成熟，可以承担责任，
AND IT WAS STUPID OF ME
TO THINK
真是太傻了。
YOU WERE MATURE ENOUGH
TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
（音乐震耳欲聋）
( music blaring )
* 当危险四伏时 *
* WHO'S THE CAT
THAT WON'T COP OUT *
* 谁是那个不退缩的家伙？
* WHEN THERE'S DANGER
ALL ABOUT? *
* 沙夫特 *
* SHAFT *
* 没错 *
* RIGHT ON
* 他们说这个家伙，沙夫特，是个狠角色…… *
* THEY SAY THIS CAT, SHAFT,
IS A BAD MOTHER... *
* 闭嘴 *
* SHUT YOUR MOUTH *
* 但我说的是沙夫特 *
* BUT I'M TALKIN' 'BOUT SHAFT
* 我们懂他 *
* WE CAN DIG IT *
* 他是个复杂的人 *
* HE'S A COMPLICATED MAN
* 但除了他的女人，没人懂他 *
* BUT NO ONE UNDERSTANDS HIM
BUT HIS WOMAN *
* 约翰·沙夫特 *
* JOHN SHAFT *
我从不知道你没有节奏感。
I NEVER KNEW
YOU DIDN'T HAVE RHYTHM.
（咯咯笑）
( giggling )
来吧，宝贝。
COME ON, BABY.
你把一首最伟大的歌搞砸了。
YOU'RE MESSING UP
ONE OF THE GREATEST SONGS.
那是什么？
WHAT IS THAT?
那是我的手鼓。
IT'S MY TAMBOURINE.